Reaper
here well you sure take to this bad guy
thing easily don't you and you sure know
how to play Boy
Scout aren't you supposed to be dead
didn't
take one of these days someone's going
to put an end to you I invite them to
try
guess you're going back on my list Anna
what happened to you
Gabriel I shouldn't be surprised you
took his side you never gave me much
choice just like all
times right except for the part where
you became a homicidal
murderer I taught you everything you
know not
everything I didn't teach you all my
tricks lucky for me I still have a few
tricks of my own you look
ridiculous looked in the mirror lately
you weren't giving those guns to toss
him around like trash I don't take
lessons from
you what happened to you you tell me
Duc looks like we're were working
together again let's hope it goes better
than the time at the
Museum poor Winston has to hide away so
he doesn't scare the children I don't
even think children are afraid of
you try to stick to the plan Sombra look
someone has to be ready when all your
careful planning doesn't pan out what's
the plan today Gabe you don't mind if I
call you Gabe do you stick to the
mission so what are we doing here boss I
need to pay a visit to a
friend you look like the kind of guy who
could use something blown up a candidate
just came to
mind you chose your
side I didn't teach you all my tricks
should have paid closer
attention you never were a good
student tin cans a dime a
dozen another name off my
list another one off the
list never liked you
much this is how it should have
been you always did have a high opinion
of
yourself still trying to play Hero
monkey stupid
monkey actions have
consequences make a lot of threats and
someone's going to shut you up you never
fooled
me too smart for your own good not so
smart now